Guide to the Lindseth Collection of Alice Ephemera MSS.368
Fales Library and Special Collections
Lindseth Collection of Alice in Wonderland Ephemera
1900-2015
1930-1970
Fales Library and Special Collections
Montgomery, Lall G.
MSS.368
67 Linear Feet in 27 record cartons, 18 manuscript boxes, 31 flat boxes, 3 shared oversize boxes, 6 oversize folders, 1 rolled storage tube, 1 box binder, and 3 unhoused art objects.
The Lindseth Collection of Alice in Wonderland Ephemera comprises toys, auction catalogs, games, housewares, dolls, posters, books, vinyl sound discs and art relating to Alice in Wonderland collected by Dr. Lall Montgomery. This collection documents Alice in Wonderland in American popular culture.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Arrangement
The Lindseth Collection of Alice in Wonderland Ephemera is organized by series and then by object. When applicable, certain items have the following information: Title, Description and Dimension.
Oversized items are located at the end of the finding aid.
Researchers should be aware that there is some overlap between contents of the series. Some material, such as clippings and calendars, can be found in multiple series of the collection.
The Collection is arranged into 9 Series:
Series I: Auction Catalogs
Series II: Housewares/Decorations
Series III: Games/Dolls/Toys/Puppets
Series V: Printed Ephemera
Series IV: Photographs/Slides
Series VII: Books/Magazines/Clippings/Newspapers
Series VIII: Art
Series IX: Media
Biographical Note
The bulk of the material was acquired by Dr. Lall Montgomery.
Dr. Lall G. Montgomery was born in Deloraine, Manitoba in July 1902. He took his premedical work at the University of Manitoba and graduated in Medicine from the Manitoba Medical College in 1929. After graduation he spent two years in the study of tuberculosis in the Manitoba Sanatorium at Ninette, Manitoba, and then spent three years as a Fellow in Pathology in the Mayo Foundation of the University of Minnesota at the May Clinic in Rochester, Minnesota. After completing this Fellowship, he became director of the Department of Pathology and the Pathology Laboratories of the Ball Memorial Hospital, in Muncie, Indiana where he became Senior Pathologist in the Pathology Department. Dr. Lall G. Montgomery was a Founding Fellow of the College of American Pathologists, and Delegate from the Section on Pathology and Physiology to American Medical Association, President of the American Society of Clinical Pathologists, an Associate Editor of the Journal of the Indiana State Medical Association, and was a member of the Advisory Board of Medical Specialties, representing the Federation of State Medical Boards of the United States.
The Lall G. Montgomery Papers (1929-1970) are housed at Alexander M. Bracken Library, at Ball State University in Muncie Indiana.
In an article published in the January 1965 magazine Doll Collector, Dr. Montgomery says: "It may be difficult to imagine how collecting dolls may have occurred to a collector of translations, but again this will not seems as surprising to a collector as to the non-initiated; in fact this is the usual way in which any collection will branch out into many diverse fields of interest and into many seemingly unrelated ways and by-ways, such as in my case, specially illustrated editions, special biding, parodies, games, pictures, cutouts, sheet music and phonographic recordings, to mention just a few and of course, dolls."
Legal title, copyright, and literary rights reside with Archives and Special Collections, Ball State University Libraries, Muncie, IN.
Scope and Contents
The Lindseth Collection of Alice in Wonderland Ephemera comprises toys, auction catalogs, games, housewares, dolls, posters, books, vinyl sound discs and art relating to Alice in Wonderland. Dr. Lall G. Montgomery's collection represents the wide variety of different ways Alice in Wonderland and Alice Through the Looking Glass have been interpreted in American popular culture.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll, MSS.057
Related Materials
Della Thomas collection (1913-2004) housed at the Edmon Low Library at Oklahoma State University
G. Edward Cassady, M.D. and Margaret Elizabeth Cassady, R.N. Lewis Carroll collection of ephemera, housed at the USC Libraries at the University of Southern California
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and are unavailable to researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Jon Lindseth, 2015. The accession number associated with this gift is 2017.191.
Custodial History
Items in accession number 2017.191 were loaned by Jon Lindseth to the Grolier Club for an exhibit in fall 2015. The materials were then transferred to NYU in November 2015.
Coloring books; Toys.; Alice in Wonderland (Motion picture: 1951); Games for children; Carroll, Lewis, 1832-1898. Through the looking-glass; Printed ephemera.; Printed materials.; Magazines (Periodicals); Photographs.; Auction catalogs.; Dolls; Posters.; Character toys.; Puzzles; Newspapers.; Games; Carroll, Lewis, 1832-1898
- Series I: Auction and Exhibit Materials
  - Subseries A: General Catalogs A-Z
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 626, January 30, 31, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 1873, November 10, 11, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 2099, November 16, 17, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 3850, May 12, 13, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 3871, December 2, 3, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 3966, April 19, 20, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 4210, December 4, 5, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 4215, December 14, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Anderson Galleries; No. 4242, March 18, 19, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Antiquarian Book Company; No. 48, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Argus Book Shop; No. 25, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Baltimore Books; No. 279, June 30, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bauman Rare Books, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bauman Rare Books, January 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bauman Rare Books, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Beeleigh Abby Books; No. BA12, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Beeleigh Abby Books; No. BA16, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Barnet J. Beyer, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Robert K. Black; No. 13, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Robert K. Black; No. 14, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Blackwell's Rare Books; No. B107, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Blackwell's Rare Books; No. B108, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Blackwell's Rare Books; No. B114, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Blackwell's Rare Books; No. 923, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Blackwell's Rare Books, January 26, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Charles S. Boesen, [Undated] (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Charles S. Boesen; No. 2, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The Book Block; No. 4, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Bookstall; No. 22, Spring/Summer 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - James M. W. Borg, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - BuddenBooks, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - BuddenBooks, November 8, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie Book Group; No. 146, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Book and Art Auctions, December 11, 12, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Children's Bookshop, December 1, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Children's Bookshop, October 22, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Current Company, March 16, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - James Cummins Bookseller; No. 26, Spring 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - James Cummins Bookseller; No. 47, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - J. Clarke-Hall Ltd.; No. 32, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Ursula Davidson's Antiquarian Illustrated and Children's Books; No. 8, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Davis and Orioli; No. 36, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Dawsons of Pall Mall; No. 135, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Dawson Book Service; No. 34, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Lyndsay Dobson Books, Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - James F. Drake; No. 238, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - E. P. Dutton and Company, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - E. P. Dutton and Company, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Peter Eaton; No. 23, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Francis Edwards Ltd.; No. 687, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Francis Edwards Ltd.; No. 815, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Francis Edwards Ltd.; No. 933, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Francis Edwards Ltd.; No. 939, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Francis Edwards Ltd.; No. 946, May 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Francis Edwards Ltd.; No. 971, February 15, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Francis Edwards Ltd.; No. 1034, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - English Children's Books; No. 20, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Simon Finch Rare Books; No. 23, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - C. A. Kyrle Fletcher; No. 233, Autumn 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Samuel T. Freeman, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Doris Frohnsdorff; No. 10, January 21, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Doris Frohnsdorff; No. 29, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Doris Frohnsdorff; No. 59, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Thomas A. Goldwasser; No. 8, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Robin Greer; No. 82, Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Robin Greer; No. 79, Summer 1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Joshua Heller Rare Books; No. 10, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Stan V. Henkels; No. 1417, June 27, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Stan V. Henkels; No. 1420, November 8, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Stan V. Henkels; No. 1430, April 24, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Stan V. Henkels; No. 1448, November 13, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Heritage Book Shop Inc., [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Heritage Book Shop Inc., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Heritage Book Shop Inc.; No. 198, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Daniel Hirsch Books; No. 16, November 16, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Hodgson and Company; No. 20, April 29, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Hodgson and Company; No. 19, May 10, 11, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Hodgson and Company; No. 15, March 27, 28, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Hodgson and Company; No. 13, April 27, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - John Howell Books; No. 34, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - J. and S. Graphics; No. 16, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - J. and S. Graphics; No. 21, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Japanese, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Jenkins Company; No. 108, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Jenkins Company; No. 155, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - David P. Johnson Bookseller, Autumn 1974 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Ewen Kerr Books; No. 31, September 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - H. P. Kraus; No. 133, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - H. P. Kraus; No. 141, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Lakin and Marley Rare Books; No. 1, November 16, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Tom Lloyd Roberts Antiquarian Bookseller; No. 65, June 1990 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - A. L. Mabee Books; No. 2, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - David Magee Antiquarian Books, Part 1, A-J, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - David Magee Antiquarian Books, Part 2, K-Z, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - David Magee Antiquarian Books, Part 3, Mixed Pickles, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - David Mayou, [Undated] (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - George S. MacManus Co.; No. 226, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - George S. MacManus Co.; No. 238, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - George S. MacManus Co.; No. 252, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - George S. MacManus Co.; No. 269, June 6, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - George S. MacManus Co.; No. 278, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Merwin Sales Company, March 9, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Mark E. Mitchell Inc.; No. 18, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd.; No. 7, Spring 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - National Art Galleries Inc., Part 1, February 23, 24, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Maurice F. Neville Rare Books; No. 7, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Maurice F. Neville Rare Books; No. 8, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Ernest Dressel North, November 1927 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Oak Knoll Books; No. 131, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Oak Knoll Books; No. M531, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Pepper and Stern Rare Books Inc., February 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Philips, November 9, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Philip J. Pirages, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 697, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 743, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 799, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 807, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 843, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 898, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 900, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 910, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; No. 931, December 26, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Rains Gallery, December 1935 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Rains Gallery, April 1937 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Ritter-Hopson Galleries Inc., December 15, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Ritter-Hopson Galleries Inc., December 15, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Ritter-Hopson Galleries Inc., March 16, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Rosenbach Company, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Bertram Rota; No. 32, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bertram Rota, January 23, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Rowfant Book Shop; No. 7, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Jo Ann Rzisler Ltd.; No. 29, Winter 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Walter Schatzki; No. 1, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Justin G. Schiller Ltd.; No 42, December 1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Justin G. Schiller Ltd.; No. 46, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Hellmut Schumann; No. 499, January 2, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Hellmut Schumann; No. 559, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Michael Silverman; No. 2, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Silo's, January 23, 24, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - G. F. Simmons, November 15, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Henry Sothern Ltd., Summer 1987 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Henry Sothern Ltd., Winter 1996 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Barbara Stone Rare Books; No. 52, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Barbara Stone Rare Books; No. 71, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Bell and Storm Inc.; No. 2, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Swann Auction Galleries, November 6, 7, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Swann Art Galleries, April 4, 5, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Swann Auction Galleries, April 26, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Swann Galleries, April 30, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Swann Galleries, December 3, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Swann Galleries, October 15, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Swann Galleries, November 7, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Swann Galleries, October 8, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Swann Galleries, March 5, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Swann Galleries, April 21, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Swann Galleries, February 8, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - John Wilson; No. 62, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Ulysses Bookshop, [Undated] (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Union Art Gallery; No. 56, February 13, 14, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Union Art Gallery, April 24, 25, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Montgomery Ward and Company; No. K, 1896-1897 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Subseries B: Christie's Catalogs
    - Christie's, February 6, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Christie's, June 24, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Christie's, April 26, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Christie's, December 8, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Christie's, April 20, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Christie's, July 18, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Christie's, December 11, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Christie's, June 9, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Christie's, October 22, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Christie's, November 20, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Christie's, March 18, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Christie's, October 7, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Christie's, October 19, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Christie's, November 16, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Christie's, June 28, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Christie's, October 19, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Christie's, December 15, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Christie's, May 1, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: Sotheby Catalogs
    - Sotheby, Wilkinson and Hodge, December 17, 18, 19, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 6, 7, 8, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 25, 26, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 17, 18, 19, 20, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 14, 15, 16, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 15, 16, 17, 18, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 13, 14, 15, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 30, 31, and June 1, 2, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 7, 8, 9, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 30, and May 1, 2, 3, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 4, 5, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 16, 17, 18, 19, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 27, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 31, August 1, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Sotheby and Co., August 2, 3, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 29, 30, 31, August 1, 2, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Sotheby and Co., February 17, 18, 19, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 14, 15, 16, 17, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 16, 17, 18, 19, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 28, 29, 30, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 15, 16, 17, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 6, 7, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 28, 29, 30, 31, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 25, 26, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 27, 28, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 14, 15, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 3, 4, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 3, 4, 5, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 18, 19, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 31, August 1, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Sotheby and Co., August 2, 3, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 13, 14, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 20, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 23, 24, 25, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 18, 19, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 16, 17, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 23, 24, 25, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 30, 31, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 18, 19, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 20, 21, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 1, 2, 3, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 18, 19, 20, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 8, 9, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 20, 21, 22, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 27, 28, 29, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 15, 16, 17, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 26, 27, 28, 29, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 14, 15, 16, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 19, 20, 21, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 15, 16, 17, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 23, 24, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Sotheby and Co., April, 11, 12, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 25, 26, 27, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 31, August 1, 2, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 26, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 27, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 24, 25, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 4, 5, 6, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 5, 6, 7, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 9, 10, 11, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 25, 26, 27, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 8, 9, 10, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 25, 26, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 28, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Sotheby and Co., February 18, 19, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 13, 14, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 15, 16, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 22, 23, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Sotheby and Co., May 25, 26, 27, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 27, 28, 29, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 15, 16, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 6, 7, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Sotheby and Co., October 11, 12, 13, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 14, 15, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 21, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 6, 7, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Sotheby and Co., June 12, 13, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 21, 22, 23, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Sotheby and Co., December 11, 12, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Sotheby and Co., January 22, 23, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 8, 9, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Sotheby and Co., October 28, 29, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 23, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 3, 4, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 24, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 16, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 16, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 23, 24, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 19, 20, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 13, 14, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Sotheby and Co., February 19, 20, 21, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Sotheby's, July 24, 25, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Sotheby's, June 27, 28, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Subseries D: Parke-Bernet Catalogs
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 23, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 2, 3, 4, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., February 1, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 12, 13, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 3, 4, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 28, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., December 5, 6, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 30, May 1, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., February 26, 27, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 18, 19, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 29, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 1, 2, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 29, 30, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 26, 27, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., October 18, 19, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., October 16, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., December 4, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)